

### Profile

Seasoned professional with more than nine years of experience working as a full-stack developer and tech lead. Hands-on experience with technologies such as Angular+, .NET Core, Microsoft Azure.

-

Well-experienced in working with large and geographically diverse teams across multiple time zones. Able to fulfil tasks within a short time frame and in a coordinated manner.

# Employment History

Senior Consultant, Remote

July 2023 — Present

Engineering Manager at Marsh McLennan, Mumbai

March 2023 — June 2023

Senior Engineering Lead at Persistent Systems, Remote

March 2022 — March 2023

Tech Lead at Ness Digital Engineering, Remote

February 2020 — March 2022

Senior Software Engineer at Clover Infotech, Mumbai

September 2019 — January 2020

Senior Software Engineer at Lionbridge Technologies, Mumbai

June 2017 — August 2018

Support Engineer at Rolla Computers Sharjah, Remote

February 2015 — June 2017

**Freelancer** 

September 2013 — February 2015

Software Developer at Sundaram Technologies, Mumbai

December 2012 — August 2013

### Education

Bachelor of Engineering, Mumbai University, Mumbai

June 2003 — May 2010

ASP.NET Diploma, Seed Infotech, Mumbai

May 2012 — November 2012

Desktop & Windows Application Development, NIIT, Mumbai

September 2008 — November 2009

AZ 900 Azure Fundamentals, Microsoft, Remote

July 2021 — July 2021

#### **Details**

+918652715392

chadangat@gmail.com

Date of birth

2nd April 1984

#### Skills

Microsoft Azure

**Angular** 

ASP.NET Core

ASP.NET MVC

Git

**SSRS** 

**Azure Boards** 

Jira

Microsoft SQL Server

C#

JavaScript

jQuery

**VB.NET** 

ASP.NET Web Forms

Windows Forms

#### Languages

English

Hindi

Marathi

### **Hobbies**

Watching YouTube to keep up with latest trends in technology, hardware. - Contributing to open-source projects on GitHub

# Project Summary

#### **Insurance Broker Payment Gateway Integration, Marsh McLennan**

March 2023 — June 2023

Led a team of developers for payment gateway integration using .NET Core Web API and C#. Reviewed and prepared architecture diagram for the API integration, REST calls, and database design.

## **App Modernization, Persistent Systems**

March 2022 — March 2023

Migrated Legacy ASP.NET MVC code to .NET Core. Converted feature modules of legacy performance appraisal application to micro services using technologies such as AWS EKS, ECS, Docker Containers.

Revamped the legacy razor-based user interface to Angular front-end with custom component library.

### **App Modernization and Maintenance, Ness Technologies**

February 2020 — March 2022

Led team of four developers in application modernization and migration of legacy application to the Azure platform.

Technologies used were ASP.NET Core, Angular, Azure key-vault, App service, Azure SQL MI, Application Insights, ADO, Azure Boards

#### **Legacy Application Maintenance, Clover Infotech**

September 2019 — January 2020

Performed maintenance and support tasks related to ASP.NET Web forms and MVC motor insurance web application.

# Microsoft NLP & Data Science Applications, Lionbridge

June 2017 — August 2018

Cleaning and parsing text-based datasets with C# tools and Microsoft data annotation libraries for variety of languages. These datasets are used to refine grammar experience in Microsoft Word, Excel, Office suite of applications.

## Point of Sale Application Development, Rolla Computers

February 2015 — May 2017

Work involved developing custom modules for the Samba POS point of sale application catering to takeaway, restaurant business. Technologies used were C#.NET, WPF, Windows Forms, windows services, SQL server.

## **Barcoding Application, Sundaram Tech**

December 2012 — August 2013

Worked on industrial printer, and camera integration using .NET libraries and API such as Halcon, Matrox and Cognex. Built custom colour detection library using .NET.

### ■ References

References available upon request